bodogaffiliate.com 2009-06-16

# Poker, Sportsbook, Casino Affiliate Programs - Bodog Affiliate

Any private information received by Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room WILL NOT be given out to anyone or any organization; it WILL NEVER be sold or distributed in any form, or for any purpose unless approved by the account holder. Therefore, client information collected by Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room is the property of Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room and is not shared with any third party, including merchants. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room is dedicated to providing useful, relevant and valuable information to our customers and subscribers. To do this, we offer an assortment of ongoing, daily, weekly and monthly publications. By opting to receive email from Bodog a client is automatically subscribed to the following publications:

BodogNation - Monthly   
BodogNation is a resource for the online gambling industry, providing humorous, informative and opinionated news about the happenings in the worlds of sports, poker, casino and entertainment. BodogNation also provides readers with monthly pictorials featuring Bodog Girls and the opportunity to contribute to The Nation Mailbag. BodogNation is THE destination for the entire Bodog community. 

Special Promotional Offers - Ongoing   
Receive information and/or offers on any new Bodog Sportsbook, Racebook, Casino or Poker Room bonus, promotion, or event.

Service Announcements - As Needed   
Important messages concerning any temporary site or system outages, plus any maintenance issues that may affect the level of service.

News Releases - Ongoing   
Receive all the latest breaking news and expert analysis of popular games and industry trends, including announcements of all new Bodog odds and specialty props. 

To assure the quality of client communications, Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room provides clients with the opportunity to view or modify their subscription preferences at any time simply by logging into their account and selecting "Manage Subscriptions" from the "Manage Account" screen. 

It is possible for a client to opt-out of receiving email from Bodog; however, there is a minimum level of communication needed for a client to play effectively, so everyone with a Bodog account will receive a "Welcome" email, containing valuable account information, along with "Service Announcements". 

If at any time a client indicates that he or she no longer wants to receive communications from Bodog, or if he or she wishes to change or correct any previously provided information, the client may send an email outlining the request to [service@bodog.com](mailto:service@bodog.com) or call the customer service center toll-free at 1-888-263-0000.

Qualified Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room staff have access to account numbers, account holder names, telephone numbers, addresses, and email addresses. Clients can change their password directly on the Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room web site (under "Manage Account/Change Password"). 

If a client needs to change their address, email address and/or telephone number, they should submit their changes directly from the Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room web site (under "Manage Account/Change Address"). New information will be verified with card-issuing banks and updated accordingly. Clients must ensure that card-issuing banks have their new address and phone number PRIOR to submitting their Profile Updates.

Clients who lose their account login information may retrieve it via the "Forgot your account number?" and "Forgot your password?" options found on the "Sign In" screen of the Bodog web site. All changes made to account holder information, whether done online or by telephone, are logged. It is the policy of Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room not to change an account holder's name unless we have an official name change notification on file (e.g. marriage certificate, notice of name change). 

If an individual becomes aware that personal information we maintain about that individual is inaccurate, or if an individual would like to update or review his or her personal information, the individual may contact us using the contact information below. As a security precaution, we may request that the individual provide identifying information such as name, address, birth date, etc. In addition, we may limit or deny access to personal information where providing such access would be unreasonably burdensome or expensive in the circumstances, or as otherwise permitted by the Safe Harbor Agreement. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room uses cookies to track how and when customers use the site. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving your passwords and other preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find most major web sites use them. Cookies also help us to see which areas of the site are popular and which are not. We can then improve the site based on this information. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room also log IP addresses for system administration purposes. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your wagering account. Bodog download products also record a unique computer ID. 

The advertisements appearing on Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please visit: <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>

The Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room website contains links to other sites; we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. Bodog will obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy at the time of collection. 

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us at [service@bodog.com](mailto:service@bodog.com). You may also contact Bodog at: 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker   
Oficentro Sabana Sur   
San Jose, Costa Rica   
International Phone: 506-296-6338   
North American Phone: 1-888-263-0000 

Last Updated: April 2006
